1. Install Java : JDK 1.8+
2. Install Node
3. Android SDK

4. Setup Java Enviornment Variable

Create an environment variable with the Java SDK path: Windows → Search → 	System → Advanced System Settings → Environment variables → New


	JAVA_HOME: C:\path\to\JavaSDK

5. Setup Android Environment variable

Due to a custom Android SDK installation location I also had to set an extra environment variable:

ANDROID_HOME: C:\path\to\AndroidSDK


6. Install react-native client
	
	$npm install -g react-native-cli

7. Create Project
	$react-native init AwesomeProject


8. Start project
your android/app/build.gradle file to use your installed version of Android SDK (I had to change mine from 23.0.1 to 23.0.3)



$react-native run-android


9. start manually
Manually start the packager (doesn’t currently start automatically on Windows, but probably will at some point in the future)
$react-native start


